porkbun.com 2016-11-25

# porkbun.com | privacy policy

Privacy Policy

THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME ("Policy"), GOVERNS THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU WHEN YOU ACCESS THIS WEBSITE (the "SITE"). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, DO NOT USE THE SITE.

THIS POLICY IS PART OF AND INCORPORATED INTO THE SITE TERMS OF SERVICE (the "Terms"). BY PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION OR OTHER INFORMATION TO US OR BY USING OUR SITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY AND THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THE POLICY.

1\. INFORMATION YOU GIVE US

We collect any information you enter on the Site or give us in any other way (such as through an email, survey, or letter). The information that we collect varies depending upon how you use our Site.

2\. AUTOMATIC INFORMATION COLLECTION

A. Cookies.

Like many websites, we use "cookies". Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We use persistent, identifying cookies to remember your information and to link your activities to you. While you can take steps to warn off, block or disable cookies, if you do, the Site may not function and appear as we have designed it. Nonetheless, if you want to take these steps, you can do so by following the instructions associated with your browser. Our cookies collect information such as:

i. the domain name and host from which you access the Internet and the Internet address of the site from which you direct-linked to ours;

ii. the date and time you access the Site and pages you visit;

iii. your computer's IP address and information about its operating system, platform and the Web browser type and version you use; and

iv. demographic and other non-personally identifiable profile information about you; and information to combat fraud or misuse.

B. Pixel Tags.

If we email you, our emails may use "pixel tags" to determine if your email software or site can display html-formatted email (this helps us optimize the size of our email messages and conserve bandwidth).

C. Collection of Information by Third Parties.

We may use a number of third-party widgets / applications as part of our website. In such a case, each of the suppliers of these widgets may set cookies to track the use of their widgets and provide the best user experience associated with the widgets' functionality. The information collected by third party cookies is subject to the privacy policy of the third party, not this Policy.

3\. OUR USE AND RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION

A. Use of Personal Information. We use personal information that you submit to us for such purposes as responding to your requests; monitoring and providing the Site; enforcing our rights and the rights of third parties, investigating and ensuring compliance with the Terms, and for marketing, providing and enhancing our services.

B. Use of Other Information. We use other information about our users for purposes such as measuring the number of visitors to sections of our Site, making the Site more useful to visitors and delivering targeted advertising and non-advertising content. We use IP addresses to, among other things, analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate, non-personally identifiable use.

C. Retention of Information. We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to any applicable law, if any, that specifically requires the handling or retention of information.

4\. OUR SHARING OF INFORMATION

We share information with third parties, without limitation as described in this Section 4.

A. We share your information with our commercial partners who provide services to our Site and/or customers.

B. WHOIS

We are required by the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN"), the organization that assumes responsibility for domain name allocation, to collect information about you during the domain name registration process. This information includes your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number. ICANN then requires all registrars to make your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the name server information associated with your domain name, to the public via an interactive Web page and a "port 43" WHOIS service. For the purposes of this Policy we will refer to this information as your "WHOIS Information." Please note that we may not be able to control how members of the public may use the WHOIS Information.

C. Advertisers and Others.

We share non-personally identifiable information with advertisers, site providers, and other persons with whom we conduct business. Conversely, these advertisers, site providers, and other persons may share with us information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

D. Third Parties.

We contract with affiliated and non-affiliated third parties to provide services to us or to you on our behalf. Examples include providing marketing assistance and analyzing data. These third parties have access to personal information needed to perform their functions.

E. Business Transfer.

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets, or engage in acquisitions, mergers, restructurings, changes of control, or similar transactions. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, customer information may be transferred to a bankruptcy trustee or debtor in possession and then to a subsequent purchaser.

F. Affiliates.

We may share user information with our corporate affiliates. Corporate affiliates are those entities that we control, are controlled by us, or are under common control with us and any joint venture in which any of the controlled entities may participate from time to time. Conversely, we may obtain information about you from our corporate affiliates or from your visits to other web sites that we or our corporate affiliates control.

G. Compliance and Safety.

We may release user information when we believe release is appropriate to:

i. comply with applicable law, and to respond to legal process, including subpoenas, search warrants and court orders, and to respond to or otherwise address written complaints of copyright infringement;

ii. make disclosures under programs intended to prevent potential crimes or investigate persons;

iii. enforce or apply agreements, including the Terms; or

iv. protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, our users, or others, including exchanging information with other companies for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

5\. INFORMATION SECURITY

A. Your Obligations.

You must protect against unauthorized access to your personal information and to your computer. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE TO ENSURE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

B. Our Security Measures.

We have physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use your information. HOWEVER, WE DO NOT GUARANTEE SECURITY. Neither people nor security systems are foolproof, including encryption systems.

6\. LINKS

The Site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects your personally identifiable information. This Policy applies only to information collected by the Site.

7\. CHOICE

If you have provided us your email or other contact information, then we reserve the right to send you customary business communications.

8\. CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS

A. Privacy Concerns.

Your use of the Site and any dispute over privacy is subject to the Terms. If you have any concern about privacy practices of Porkbun, then please send us a thorough description to legal@porkbun.com, and we will try to resolve it. If you think we are in default of the Terms, then you may contact us at our legal notices address in Section 9 below.

B. Notice Required by Law.

In those jurisdictions that permit email notice, if we are required to disclose or provide notice of invasion of certain security systems, we will do so by email to the most current email address provided by you to us.

C. Identity Theft.

If you believe that you are a victim of identity theft entitled by law to request information from us, write us at our Legal Notice address (see Section 9) and we will let you know what additional information you must provide to us. After we have received that information, we will supply without charge the information legally required to be disclosed that we then have, subject to applicable law and reserving all of our rights and defenses.

9\. CONTACT INFORMATION AND INFORMATION ABOUT ENFORCEMENT OF OUR POLICY.

For customer matters (including questions relating to this Policy), you may email us at info@porkbun.com. To send us a legal notice, mail it by certified mail (return receipt requested) to: 

Porkbun LLC

650 Greystone Park NE

Atlanta, GA  30324
